He had to meet her - to find himself!
Bobby Deerfield is a drama, romance film directed by Sydney Pollack.
Bobby Deerfield, a famous American race car driver on the European circuit, falls
in love with the enigmatic Lillian Morelli, who is terminally ill.
Bobby, played by Al Pacino.
Lillian, played by Marthe Keller.
Lydia, played by Anny Duperey.
The Brother, played by Walter McGinn.
Uncle Luigi, played by Romolo Valli.
The Flutist, played by Van Doude.
Bobby Deerfield is a 1977 American romantic drama film directed by
Sydney Pollack and starring Al Pacino and Marthe Keller.
Based on Erich Maria Remarque's 1961 novel Heaven Has No Favorites, it is about a famous American race car driver
on the European circuit who falls in love with an enigmatic Swiss woman who is terminally ill.
Pacino was nominated for a Golden Globe Award for
Best Actor – Motion Picture Drama.
The movie uses clips from the 1976 Formula One season.
The film explores themes of melancholy, terminal illness, race
car driver, race car crash, formula one (f1).
The tone is emotional.